- id: 2001
  question: '\( ((175 - 70) \times 11) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 385
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 175 - 70 = 105 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 105 \times 11 = 1155 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1155 \div 3 = 385 \)
- id: 2002
  question: '\( ((477 - 92) \times 12) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2310
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 477 - 92 = 385 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 385 \times 12 = 4620 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4620 \div 2 = 2310 \)
- id: 2003
  question: '\( ((216 - 82) \times 12) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 268
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 216 - 82 = 134 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 134 \times 12 = 1608 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1608 \div 6 = 268 \)
- id: 2004
  question: '\( ((694 - 67) \times 12) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 1254
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 694 - 67 = 627 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 627 \times 12 = 7524 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7524 \div 6 = 1254 \)
- id: 2005
  question: '\( ((449 - 60) \times 6) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1167
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 449 - 60 = 389 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 389 \times 6 = 2334 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2334 \div 2 = 1167 \)
- id: 2006
  question: '\( ((934 - 66) \times 9) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 2604
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 934 - 66 = 868 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 868 \times 9 = 7812 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7812 \div 3 = 2604 \)
- id: 2007
  question: '\( ((244 - 58) \times 3) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 279
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 244 - 58 = 186 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 186 \times 3 = 558 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 558 \div 2 = 279 \)
- id: 2008
  question: '\( ((381 - 62) \times 7) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 319
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 381 - 62 = 319 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 319 \times 7 = 2233 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2233 \div 7 = 319 \)
- id: 2009
  question: '\( ((408 - 68) \times 4) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 680
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 408 - 68 = 340 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 340 \times 4 = 1360 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1360 \div 2 = 680 \)
- id: 2010
  question: '\( ((183 - 57) \times 12) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 216
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 183 - 57 = 126 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 126 \times 12 = 1512 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1512 \div 7 = 216 \)
- id: 2011
  question: '\( ((873 - 20) \times 8) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 853
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 873 - 20 = 853 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 853 \times 8 = 6824 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6824 \div 8 = 853 \)
- id: 2012
  question: '\( ((735 - 61) \times 12) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 2696
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 735 - 61 = 674 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 674 \times 12 = 8088 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 8088 \div 3 = 2696 \)
- id: 2013
  question: '\( ((163 - 10) \times 5) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 255
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 163 - 10 = 153 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 153 \times 5 = 765 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 765 \div 3 = 255 \)
- id: 2014
  question: '\( ((132 - 78) \times 10) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 270
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 132 - 78 = 54 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 54 \times 10 = 540 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 540 \div 2 = 270 \)
- id: 2015
  question: '\( ((128 - 48) \times 9) \div 9 \) '
  answer: 80
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 128 - 48 = 80 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 80 \times 9 = 720 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 720 \div 9 = 80 \)
- id: 2016
  question: '\( ((288 - 16) \times 5) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 272
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 288 - 16 = 272 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 272 \times 5 = 1360 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1360 \div 5 = 272 \)
- id: 2017
  question: '\( ((584 - 88) \times 8) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 496
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 584 - 88 = 496 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 496 \times 8 = 3968 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3968 \div 8 = 496 \)
- id: 2018
  question: '\( ((817 - 41) \times 12) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 3104
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 817 - 41 = 776 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 776 \times 12 = 9312 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 9312 \div 3 = 3104 \)
- id: 2019
  question: '\( ((528 - 90) \times 9) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1971
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 528 - 90 = 438 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 438 \times 9 = 3942 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3942 \div 2 = 1971 \)
- id: 2020
  question: '\( ((585 - 30) \times 5) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 555
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 585 - 30 = 555 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 555 \times 5 = 2775 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2775 \div 5 = 555 \)
- id: 2021
  question: '\( ((222 - 12) \times 6) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 210
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 222 - 12 = 210 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 210 \times 6 = 1260 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1260 \div 6 = 210 \)
- id: 2022
  question: '\( ((773 - 24) \times 8) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2996
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 773 - 24 = 749 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 749 \times 8 = 5992 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5992 \div 2 = 2996 \)
- id: 2023
  question: '\( ((997 - 77) \times 6) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 920
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 997 - 77 = 920 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 920 \times 6 = 5520 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5520 \div 6 = 920 \)
- id: 2024
  question: '\( ((791 - 95) \times 9) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 783
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 791 - 95 = 696 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 696 \times 9 = 6264 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6264 \div 8 = 783 \)
- id: 2025
  question: '\( ((619 - 21) \times 10) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 1495
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 619 - 21 = 598 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 598 \times 10 = 5980 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5980 \div 4 = 1495 \)
- id: 2026
  question: '\( ((916 - 87) \times 4) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 829
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 916 - 87 = 829 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 829 \times 4 = 3316 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3316 \div 4 = 829 \)
- id: 2027
  question: '\( ((569 - 89) \times 7) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1680
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 569 - 89 = 480 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 480 \times 7 = 3360 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3360 \div 2 = 1680 \)
- id: 2028
  question: '\( ((605 - 29) \times 10) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2880
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 605 - 29 = 576 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 576 \times 10 = 5760 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5760 \div 2 = 2880 \)
- id: 2029
  question: '\( ((342 - 53) \times 3) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 289
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 342 - 53 = 289 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 289 \times 3 = 867 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 867 \div 3 = 289 \)
- id: 2030
  question: '\( ((821 - 72) \times 6) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2247
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 821 - 72 = 749 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 749 \times 6 = 4494 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4494 \div 2 = 2247 \)
- id: 2031
  question: '\( ((517 - 47) \times 10) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2350
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 517 - 47 = 470 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 470 \times 10 = 4700 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4700 \div 2 = 2350 \)
- id: 2032
  question: '\( ((627 - 13) \times 5) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1535
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 627 - 13 = 614 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 614 \times 5 = 3070 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3070 \div 2 = 1535 \)
- id: 2033
  question: '\( ((345 - 68) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 554
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 345 - 68 = 277 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 277 \times 10 = 2770 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2770 \div 5 = 554 \)
- id: 2034
  question: '\( ((103 - 72) \times 8) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 31
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 103 - 72 = 31 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 31 \times 8 = 248 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 248 \div 8 = 31 \)
- id: 2035
  question: '\( ((108 - 57) \times 5) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 85
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 108 - 57 = 51 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 51 \times 5 = 255 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 255 \div 3 = 85 \)
- id: 2036
  question: '\( ((488 - 21) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 934
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 488 - 21 = 467 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 467 \times 10 = 4670 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4670 \div 5 = 934 \)
- id: 2037
  question: '\( ((963 - 63) \times 11) \div 9 \) '
  answer: 1100
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 963 - 63 = 900 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 900 \times 11 = 9900 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 9900 \div 9 = 1100 \)
- id: 2038
  question: '\( ((938 - 55) \times 9) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 2649
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 938 - 55 = 883 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 883 \times 9 = 7947 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7947 \div 3 = 2649 \)
- id: 2039
  question: '\( ((806 - 90) \times 10) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 3580
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 806 - 90 = 716 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 716 \times 10 = 7160 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7160 \div 2 = 3580 \)
- id: 2040
  question: '\( ((216 - 48) \times 9) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 189
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 216 - 48 = 168 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 168 \times 9 = 1512 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1512 \div 8 = 189 \)
- id: 2041
  question: '\( ((399 - 64) \times 11) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 737
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 399 - 64 = 335 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 335 \times 11 = 3685 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3685 \div 5 = 737 \)
- id: 2042
  question: '\( ((941 - 47) \times 3) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 894
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 941 - 47 = 894 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 894 \times 3 = 2682 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2682 \div 3 = 894 \)
- id: 2043
  question: '\( ((404 - 15) \times 6) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 778
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 404 - 15 = 389 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 389 \times 6 = 2334 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2334 \div 3 = 778 \)
- id: 2044
  question: '\( ((598 - 49) \times 3) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 549
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 598 - 49 = 549 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 549 \times 3 = 1647 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1647 \div 3 = 549 \)
- id: 2045
  question: '\( ((316 - 17) \times 12) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 598
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 316 - 17 = 299 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 299 \times 12 = 3588 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3588 \div 6 = 598 \)
- id: 2046
  question: '\( ((655 - 54) \times 6) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 1202
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 655 - 54 = 601 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 601 \times 6 = 3606 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3606 \div 3 = 1202 \)
- id: 2047
  question: '\( ((690 - 79) \times 8) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2444
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 690 - 79 = 611 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 611 \times 8 = 4888 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4888 \div 2 = 2444 \)
- id: 2048
  question: '\( ((745 - 36) \times 5) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 709
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 745 - 36 = 709 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 709 \times 5 = 3545 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3545 \div 5 = 709 \)
- id: 2049
  question: '\( ((686 - 18) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 1336
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 686 - 18 = 668 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 668 \times 10 = 6680 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6680 \div 5 = 1336 \)
- id: 2050
  question: '\( ((707 - 73) \times 7) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2219
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 707 - 73 = 634 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 634 \times 7 = 4438 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4438 \div 2 = 2219 \)
- id: 2051
  question: '\( ((766 - 97) \times 6) \div 9 \) '
  answer: 446
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 766 - 97 = 669 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 669 \times 6 = 4014 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4014 \div 9 = 446 \)
- id: 2052
  question: '\( ((460 - 66) \times 9) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1773
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 460 - 66 = 394 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 394 \times 9 = 3546 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3546 \div 2 = 1773 \)
- id: 2053
  question: '\( ((336 - 68) \times 10) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 335
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 336 - 68 = 268 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 268 \times 10 = 2680 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2680 \div 8 = 335 \)
- id: 2054
  question: '\( ((567 - 55) \times 8) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 2048
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 567 - 55 = 512 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 512 \times 8 = 4096 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4096 \div 2 = 2048 \)
- id: 2055
  question: '\( ((156 - 62) \times 9) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 141
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 156 - 62 = 94 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 94 \times 9 = 846 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 846 \div 6 = 141 \)
- id: 2056
  question: '\( ((167 - 79) \times 3) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 66
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 167 - 79 = 88 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 88 \times 3 = 264 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 264 \div 4 = 66 \)
- id: 2057
  question: '\( ((853 - 14) \times 8) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 839
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 853 - 14 = 839 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 839 \times 8 = 6712 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6712 \div 8 = 839 \)
- id: 2058
  question: '\( ((383 - 75) \times 8) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1232
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 383 - 75 = 308 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 308 \times 8 = 2464 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2464 \div 2 = 1232 \)
- id: 2059
  question: '\( ((537 - 17) \times 9) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 780
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 537 - 17 = 520 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 520 \times 9 = 4680 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4680 \div 6 = 780 \)
- id: 2060
  question: '\( ((817 - 19) \times 8) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 912
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 817 - 19 = 798 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 798 \times 8 = 6384 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6384 \div 7 = 912 \)
- id: 2061
  question: '\( ((459 - 88) \times 9) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 477
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 459 - 88 = 371 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 371 \times 9 = 3339 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3339 \div 7 = 477 \)
- id: 2062
  question: '\( ((532 - 24) \times 3) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 381
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 532 - 24 = 508 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 508 \times 3 = 1524 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1524 \div 4 = 381 \)
- id: 2063
  question: '\( ((765 - 25) \times 6) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 1480
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 765 - 25 = 740 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 740 \times 6 = 4440 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 4440 \div 3 = 1480 \)
- id: 2064
  question: '\( ((505 - 79) \times 9) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1917
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 505 - 79 = 426 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 426 \times 9 = 3834 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3834 \div 2 = 1917 \)
- id: 2065
  question: '\( ((723 - 26) \times 4) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1394
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 723 - 26 = 697 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 697 \times 4 = 2788 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2788 \div 2 = 1394 \)
- id: 2066
  question: '\( ((126 - 58) \times 8) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 136
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 126 - 58 = 68 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 68 \times 8 = 544 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 544 \div 4 = 136 \)
- id: 2067
  question: '\( ((162 - 82) \times 11) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 110
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 162 - 82 = 80 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 80 \times 11 = 880 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 880 \div 8 = 110 \)
- id: 2068
  question: '\( ((463 - 30) \times 8) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 1732
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 463 - 30 = 433 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 433 \times 8 = 3464 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3464 \div 2 = 1732 \)
- id: 2069
  question: '\( ((193 - 41) \times 5) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 380
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 193 - 41 = 152 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 152 \times 5 = 760 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 760 \div 2 = 380 \)
- id: 2070
  question: '\( ((313 - 58) \times 11) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 935
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 313 - 58 = 255 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 255 \times 11 = 2805 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2805 \div 3 = 935 \)
- id: 2071
  question: '\( ((730 - 65) \times 9) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 855
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 730 - 65 = 665 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 665 \times 9 = 5985 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5985 \div 7 = 855 \)
- id: 2072
  question: '\( ((685 - 23) \times 3) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 993
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 685 - 23 = 662 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 662 \times 3 = 1986 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1986 \div 2 = 993 \)
- id: 2073
  question: '\( ((696 - 18) \times 11) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 2486
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 696 - 18 = 678 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 678 \times 11 = 7458 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7458 \div 3 = 2486 \)
- id: 2074
  question: '\( ((375 - 59) \times 5) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 395
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 375 - 59 = 316 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 316 \times 5 = 1580 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1580 \div 4 = 395 \)
- id: 2075
  question: '\( ((990 - 78) \times 6) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 1824
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 990 - 78 = 912 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 912 \times 6 = 5472 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5472 \div 3 = 1824 \)
- id: 2076
  question: '\( ((905 - 30) \times 12) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 1750
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 905 - 30 = 875 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 875 \times 12 = 10500 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 10500 \div 6 = 1750 \)
- id: 2077
  question: '\( ((907 - 20) \times 6) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 887
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 907 - 20 = 887 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 887 \times 6 = 5322 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5322 \div 6 = 887 \)
- id: 2078
  question: '\( ((404 - 97) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 614
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 404 - 97 = 307 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 307 \times 10 = 3070 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3070 \div 5 = 614 \)
- id: 2079
  question: '\( ((457 - 84) \times 4) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 746
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 457 - 84 = 373 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 373 \times 4 = 1492 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1492 \div 2 = 746 \)
- id: 2080
  question: '\( ((664 - 58) \times 11) \div 2 \) '
  answer: 3333
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 664 - 58 = 606 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 606 \times 11 = 6666 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6666 \div 2 = 3333 \)
- id: 2081
  question: '\( ((912 - 68) \times 3) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 844
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 912 - 68 = 844 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 844 \times 3 = 2532 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2532 \div 3 = 844 \)
- id: 2082
  question: '\( ((242 - 42) \times 11) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 440
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 242 - 42 = 200 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 200 \times 11 = 2200 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2200 \div 5 = 440 \)
- id: 2083
  question: '\( ((657 - 14) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 1286
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 657 - 14 = 643 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 643 \times 10 = 6430 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 6430 \div 5 = 1286 \)
- id: 2084
  question: '\( ((267 - 35) \times 3) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 174
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 267 - 35 = 232 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 232 \times 3 = 696 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 696 \div 4 = 174 \)
- id: 2085
  question: '\( ((122 - 80) \times 8) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 112
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 122 - 80 = 42 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 42 \times 8 = 336 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 336 \div 3 = 112 \)
- id: 2086
  question: '\( ((529 - 20) \times 10) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 1018
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 529 - 20 = 509 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 509 \times 10 = 5090 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5090 \div 5 = 1018 \)
- id: 2087
  question: '\( ((658 - 42) \times 3) \div 4 \) '
  answer: 462
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 658 - 42 = 616 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 616 \times 3 = 1848 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1848 \div 4 = 462 \)
- id: 2088
  question: '\( ((516 - 88) \times 3) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 214
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 516 - 88 = 428 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 428 \times 3 = 1284 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1284 \div 6 = 214 \)
- id: 2089
  question: '\( ((510 - 21) \times 3) \div 9 \) '
  answer: 163
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 510 - 21 = 489 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 489 \times 3 = 1467 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1467 \div 9 = 163 \)
- id: 2090
  question: '\( ((645 - 55) \times 12) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 1180
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 645 - 55 = 590 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 590 \times 12 = 7080 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 7080 \div 6 = 1180 \)
- id: 2091
  question: '\( ((938 - 47) \times 11) \div 9 \) '
  answer: 1089
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 938 - 47 = 891 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 891 \times 11 = 9801 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 9801 \div 9 = 1089 \)
- id: 2092
  question: '\( ((445 - 90) \times 6) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 710
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 445 - 90 = 355 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 355 \times 6 = 2130 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2130 \div 3 = 710 \)
- id: 2093
  question: '\( ((157 - 75) \times 5) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 82
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 157 - 75 = 82 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 82 \times 5 = 410 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 410 \div 5 = 82 \)
- id: 2094
  question: '\( ((174 - 76) \times 3) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 49
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 174 - 76 = 98 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 98 \times 3 = 294 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 294 \div 6 = 49 \)
- id: 2095
  question: '\( ((158 - 99) \times 5) \div 5 \) '
  answer: 59
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 158 - 99 = 59 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 59 \times 5 = 295 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 295 \div 5 = 59 \)
- id: 2096
  question: '\( ((974 - 65) \times 6) \div 6 \) '
  answer: 909
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 974 - 65 = 909 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 909 \times 6 = 5454 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 5454 \div 6 = 909 \)
- id: 2097
  question: '\( ((541 - 30) \times 7) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 511
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 541 - 30 = 511 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 511 \times 7 = 3577 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3577 \div 7 = 511 \)
- id: 2098
  question: '\( ((438 - 88) \times 11) \div 7 \) '
  answer: 550
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 438 - 88 = 350 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 350 \times 11 = 3850 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 3850 \div 7 = 550 \)
- id: 2099
  question: '\( ((763 - 61) \times 4) \div 3 \) '
  answer: 936
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 763 - 61 = 702 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 702 \times 4 = 2808 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 2808 \div 3 = 936 \)
- id: 2100
  question: '\( ((298 - 70) \times 8) \div 8 \) '
  answer: 228
  solution: |-
    **Inside Brackets** \( 298 - 70 = 228 \) <br />
    **Outside Brackets** \( 228 \times 8 = 1824 \) <br />
    **Division** \( 1824 \div 8 = 228 \)
